thetollroads.com 2018-03-31

# Privacy Policy | The Toll Roads

The Toll Roads respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy tells you:

  * Why we gather information about our customers
  * What type of information we gather
  * How we learn about our customers
  * How we protect what we know about our customers
  * How we use customer information and categories of third-party persons or entities with whom we may share customer information
  * What privacy issues arise with links to other sites?
  * How you may review or request changes to your personal information
  * Your California Privacy Rights
  * About The Toll Roads Privacy Policy and how we will notify you of any material changes in our Privacy Policy

#### Why we gather information about our customers:

We need to know some personal information about you to facilitate enrollment processing and account maintenance, and to better serve you. We may also need information from you and others to help us verify your identity in order to prevent fraud and ensure security.

#### What type of information we gather:

In order to provide the services you requested, we need your first and last name, address, telephone number, email address, vehicle information and license plate number, credit card number and/or other bank account or payment information, billing address, and other basic account information required to perform account functions such as billing, account settlement, or enforcement activities.

#### How we learn about our customers:

What we know about you we obtain from you. We may also have to find out more about you from other sources in order to make sure that what we know about you is correct and complete. Those sources may include the California Department of Motor Vehicles and public records. Some of our sources may give us reports, and they may disclose what they know about you to others.

Cookies.  Cookies are files that contain information created by a web server that can be stored on a user's hard disk for use either during a particular session ("per-session" cookie) or for future use ("persistent" cookie).  We use cookies only to facilitate automated activity, determine appropriate solicitations, and review navigation patterns. Cookies are not used to disseminate contact information about website users over the Internet or to analyze any personal or confidential information that users have knowingly or unknowingly provided.

#### How we protect what we know about our customers:

We treat what we know about you confidentially and we take care in handling your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we strive to maintain physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to secure the information we collect online. This includes the use of the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) for processing transactions or account maintenance; however, no transmission or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

#### How we use what we know about our customers

and categories of third-party persons or entities with whom we may share customer information:

We may use anything we know about you to help us serve you better. We only use it and disclose it to others to the extent legally authorized. We may share your information to the extent legally authorized with third party entities such as law enforcement, government entities, and other FasTrak® toll operators as deemed necessary in order to:

  * Help us evaluate your request for a service
  * Help us process claims and other transactions
  * Confirm or correct what we know about you
  * Help us prevent fraud, money laundering, and other crimes by verifying what we know about you
  * Help us run our business
  * Process data and financial transactions for us
  * Perform research for us
  * Audit our business
  * Help us comply with the law

Children.  This Website is not directed toward children under 13 years of age nor do we knowingly collect information from children under 13.  If you are under 13, please do not submit any personally identifiable information to us or via this website.

#### What Privacy Issues Arise with Links to Other Sites?

Our website contains links that lead to other websites. We have no control over and are not responsible for the privacy policies or content of such sites.

#### How you may review or request changes to your personal information:

You may review or request changes to your personal information by accessing your FasTrak® or ExpressAccount® information online or you may call (949) 727-4800 during normal business hours.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

Except as required by law, we will not disclose your information to any third party for direct marketing purposes without your express written consent. If you have provided consent, California law permits residents of California to request certain details about information we disclose to third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to request this information, please contact us at The Toll Roads, 125 Pacifica, Ste. 120, Irvine, CA 92618

#### About The Toll Roads Privacy Policy

and how we will notify you of any material changes in our Privacy Policy:

The Toll Roads Privacy Policy may be accessed on any page of thetollroads.com website. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify our customers and users via email, mail or by means of a notice on our website. Please revisit this website for the most recent Privacy Policy.

Effective Date: 11/8/2004; Last updated 12/13/2010
